=Born Again=
=Episode 6=
- What's wrong?
- Lu Qingyuan,
I'm not feeling well.
You should go now.
What's wrong, Xiaotang?
Just go back.
I'll find you tomorrow.
Xiaotang?
Gu Xiaotang!
Are you dead or what?
You didn't take my call.
The surgery is at 10 a.m. Where are you?
The doctor and the brand
are already here.
If you dare mess with me,
- just you wait.
- Right.
My waist reduction surgery
will be performed today.
Isn't there any other way?
I'm begging you.
Just bear with it.
You'll be worthy of the wedding dress
if you remove two ribs.
Don't push your luck.
Director Li,
can we think of another way?
(It's today.)
(He forces me to remove two ribs.)
Just cinch it tight.
Gu Xiaotang,
are you listening?
I'm listening. I got it.
It's seven days earlier.
Okay.
Let's
settle our score from today.
What?
You're not doing it?
Gu Xiaotang, I'm telling you,
you are now an artist of my company.
Many things are not up to you.
Today, you will have this surgery
whether you want to or not.
I'm telling you,
we've already paid the deposit.
If you don't wear our wedding dress
at the wedding a week later,
it will be a contract breach.
That's so scary.
(Gu Xiaotang's livestream)
You all see that?
This is a perfect portrait
of an influencer company
exploiting its own artists.
- What's going on?
Mei, it's over 200,000 people.
(Gu Xiaotang's livestream)
Don't scold Director Li, guys.
Just now, we were just
putting on a show for you all.
Director Li
made a very important decision today.
In order to interpret
the ultimate beauty,
he wants to personally experience
the aesthetic pressure
that women have faced.
So the one getting
plastic surgery today isn't me,
but our great
Director Li.
This is the ultimate counterattack
against the male gaze,
isn't it?
Director Li, say hello to everyone.
Thank you for the gift.
And many thanks to Mr. Wang
from our brand partner
for the great support to us, right?
Right.
Miss Gu is right.
Through Director Li,
I see an influencer company
with real commercial value and vision.
Director Li,
thank you for your sacrifice.
Dear fans,
this is Dr. Liu,
our plastic surgeon today.
Dr. Liu, I think Director Li
needs an eyelift,
a nose bridge lift,
and some chin trim.
But the key
is still his eyes.
Director Li, well...
Director Li has made
such a big decision.
Dr. Liu, just please fulfill his wish.
He will sign all the documents.
Right,
dear Director Li?
Mr. Wang,
is there really no other way?
You deal with the mess you made.
Don't be afraid, Director Li.
Haven't you always
talked about sacrificing for art?
After much thought,
I think no one can be
better suited to bear
such a blessing than you.
Xiaotang, Xiaotang, let's talk again.
Xiaotang.
Director Li,
you're awake.
Let me walk you through
the contents of this aesthetic upgrade.
Here's what we've done.
Phase one,
inner and outer canthoplasty,
lower eyelid lowering for a softer look,
and a brow lift to prevent sagging.
Phase two,
multi-dimensional facial lifting.
We used the latest generation
of protein threads
and implanted over 200 threads
in the deep layers of your skin
to ensure the lifting effect
can be firm and lasting.
Phase three,
we extracted high-quality fat
from your inner thighs
to fill your forehead,
temples,
nasolabial folds, and chin.
We also did abdominoplasty
and male chest contouring.
Dr. Liu, slow down.
Director Li just made
such a big sacrifice.
I'm afraid he can't deal with it.
Director Li,
(Hero)
look.
Here's what you look like
after the surgery.
Doesn't it look like a great hero?
Get lost!
All of you, get lost!
Gu Xiaotang,
I won't let you off.
Director Li, you just had surgery.
Don't get too excited.
Dr. Liu just performed
a full-face thread lift on you.
If the threads break,
your face will collapse.
That's right.
You guys,
go find out
where Gu Xiaotang is now.
Take her.
I will make her suffer
a hundred times what I went through.
D-Director Li,
that's kidnapping.
What's there to fear?
She's just an influencer.
Even if she disappears,
people will only think
she's faking it for clout.
After it's done,
you'll be well rewarded.
What are you waiting for?
Get out of here!
- Yes.
Mei, you seem
to care a lot about Xiaotang.
Every time I want to deal with her,
you always try to stop me.
Right?
D-Director,
I-I didn't.
You didn't?
You think I really don't know?
Your mother's sickness
takes a lot of money every month,
and who's been paying that?
It's me.
If you weren't still of some use,
she would've been dead long ago!
I'm giving you
one last chance to make up for it.
Go
and lure Gu Xiaotang out for me.
I know she still trusts you now.
D-Director,
- I-I...
- You won't?
Fine. Then don't expect
next month's medical bills
to be covered.
Do you want to save
Xiaotang, who can't even
protect herself,
or save your mother's life?
It's up to you.
Director Li is down.
(First Loop)
But there's still Lu Qingyuan
and her mother.
(Counterattack Lu Qingyuan and Xia Na)
And Xia Na.
I must take control of the initiative
before they make a move.
But in this loop,
I can only rely on myself.
I can't involve Ye Shen again.
Who is it?
Xiaotang. Xiaotang, it's me.
Mei?
Mei, wait a moment.
What's wrong, Mei?
Who are you?
Let me go!
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪